[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most people have a ____ notion of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We did not ____ our selections on an author's nationality, religion, politics, or field of study; nor on an author's race or gender.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be aware of its almost constant presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to ____ with it.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ advantage of a strong academic vocabulary is that it helps you to read school textbooks more efficiently.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The grade will be amended but the former grade will remain on the record with an ____ notation.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We can only ____ that Fulton was already too deeply committed to his own plan to consider alternative ideas.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "During this ____ she developed her ideas on art, her main one being that the best art did not focus on reality but evoked the state of the soul.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was given to the grandmother by her grandfather in 1852, when the ____ was a member of the California assembly.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "latter", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Your password should ____ only letters or numbers.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The internet is a vast ____ for today's students.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Car companies spend a considerable ____ of money advertising their products.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Because multicultural audiences will likely become more and more common, you will need to ____ cultural differences when you analyze your audience.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The percentage of online adults who say they ____ ever or never search for health information has dropped to 39 percent.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I think your ____ is wrong. You should be in science class now, not ESL.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This page includes ____ relating to the continuing controversy over the teaching of evolution and creationism in schools.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The University of Washington has agreed to ____ a class-action lawsuit over faculty salaries.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "suspend", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I found a ____ of her homework on the cafeteria. It looked like half the school had stepped on it!", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The monks found it difficult to adapt to changes in society and in the economy, and they also found it difficult to adapt to challenges presented by the new learning made available through translations of ____ Greek texts by way of Arabic.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If children of seven years and older will be included in the study, an ____ agreement is necessary.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "sphere", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Our ____ problem is how to convince the governors that we are right.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is now clear to me that they shared an utter inability to ____ themselves objectively and critically.", "Opt_1": "encourage", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "view", "Opt_1_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A ____ method of learning vocabulary is to write words and their translations in a small notebook.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Gandhi, who brought independence to India, was an ____ man.", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government should ____ all its energy to reducing unemployment.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is interesting to think about how teaching will ____ under the influence of digital technologies.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "evolve", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We need to ____ a test to measure the improvement in ESL students' English from one year to the next.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Class data will be collected to compare perceived overweight and attempt at dieting with ____ weight risk classification.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This ____ can be applied to various educational and medical issues.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ASVAB is a ____ ability test given to all potential entrants to the Armed Services.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "stable", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you currently do not ____ the skill to meet this standard, you are advised to enroll in a class that will provide you with this capability.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The most serious ____ raised against the survey questions the use of self-report scales to assess prejudice.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many people who are old and sick are comforted by their ____ in God.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The use of gender- neutral language may seem unnecessary to some writers, but the ____ use of masculine pronouns leaves the impression that women could not be among the group to which the writer is referring.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Austen does not ____ us that a woman with Jane's mind, integrity, emotional intensity could fall and remain in love with such a dubious character.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The manager was asked to leave the company after two years of ____ performance.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The only disappointing part of the book is a portion of the third chapter, which is devoted to an interesting but much too ____ discussion of FDR's foreign policy.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to encourage the strategic thinking and action necessary to ____ and retain employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We faced an ____ problem over 10 years ago and couldn't solve it then, either.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company has decided to invest much time and ____ into marketing its new product.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "And finally, these estimates ____ to some extent on those proven numbers and, as we've already seen, those numbers are not very reliable.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "propose", "Opt_3": "ensure", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The data is ambiguous as some analysts measure this ____ according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "How do I find out whether the book is in the ____ domain?", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The strategy failed to persuade workers themselves to consider domestic ____ as anything other than a temporary transition.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "service", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Despite the political, economic and cultural success of the Arab city states, Islam for many years did not spread into the ____ of East.", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The global trade agreements have failed to ____ meaningful, enforceable labour or environmental standards.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "interrupt", "Opt_3": "constitute", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "include", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is often ____ to revise a mathematical model several times in the course of an urban operations research study.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school is will continue to undergo problems in its attempt to ____ new students unless it reduces its tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He has made ____ progress all year and should have no trouble passing his exams.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "smooth", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They ____ their nutrients from the air and not from the plant on which they are growing.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "To prevent this from happening, it is very helpful for patients to ____ talking unless absolutely necessary for three days following surgery.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "But it is not a ____ for comprehensive food safety programs throughout the food distribution system.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "quality", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "worth or value"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Do we have an ____ to help the poor?", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school has set up a ____ so that less wealthy students can attend.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is ____ that any complex society will have some sort of taxation system.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In other words, his father did not ____ the level of resources, whether they be human or monetary, necessary for success.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "accomplish", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In Ancient Rome not every ____ had equal rights.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Government agencies and aid organizations often failed to ____ people in affected communities about aid distribution and reconstruction.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Unfortunately, many drug users ____ from prison only to find themselves back there a few months later. This is because they cannot find or keep a job, and need to steal to finance their drug-taking habits.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "damage", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Despite the fact that there was a stream on the land, he could not ____ of the property at any price.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Newspaper headline: MIT scientists ____ a new way to deliver gene therapy.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most governments ____ to negotiate with kidnappers.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "refuse", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The main function of the committee is to ____ a plan for future development.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "examine", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Badly- behaved students often ____ the learning of other students in the class.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Mathews touches on an ____ that has puzzled students of American regional religious history.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "summary", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "a short account of the most important details"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ will include several basic creative thinking techniques and this theme will recur in problem-solving mode in Part 2 of the ____.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Never has the ____ of a stable, prosperous, and democratic hemisphere seemed so close within reach.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The issue is of a ____ that cannot be solved by the school alone.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Army leadership must ____ the importance of reducing energy demand to decrease costs.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "master", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There are approximately 350 students in high school. I'm not sure of the ____ number.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The word give is substituted for the word deliver to ____ more clearly the intent of the section.", "Opt_1": "specify", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "express", "Opt_1_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She very ____ comes late to class. I hope there is nothing wrong.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Typical conversations involve a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans ____ as they grow.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The nurse gave me a ____ for my headache.", "Opt_1": "plenty", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Her efforts have continued to ____ in the last few months. I think she may be having problems at home.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You will analyze recurrent patterns of international ____ conflict, identify underlying issues, and suggest alternative resolutions.", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You will receive an email from the Financial ____ office when your financial aid eligibility has been determined.", "Opt_1": "Income", "Opt_2": "Affair", "Opt_3": "Resident", "Opt_4": "Aid", "Answer": "Aid", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The fact that speech is likely to result in some violence or in destruction of property is not enough to ____ its suppression.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school received an ____ email with complaints against one of the teachers.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "anonymous", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government ____ wrote to confirm that the new law applied only to people born after the year 1990.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government ministers ____ to treat people as children to be protected from all the ills of the world.", "Opt_1": "tend", "Opt_2": "distribute", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to give out", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Everyone knows that smoking and drinking heavily is not a ____ way to live but some are addicted and cannot stop.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It's always better to be overly ____ and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "However, continuous and systematic research on the disaster did not ____ until after World War II.", "Opt_1": "entitle", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "These results are interesting, though not ____ to interpret.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the administration failed to exert its ____ to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Board will consider a leave for a President for a duration of ____ one month for each two years of service.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian ____ have in common besides being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some farmers, especially those producing corn, hope that biofuels have a bright future, both as a new ____ of cheap energy and as a new ____ of revenue.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no ____ of an original idea in this essay.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The instructor is expected to ____ his or her grading policy at the beginning of the course.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The experiment resulted in a ____ that did not seem correct.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "controversy", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Food prices are ____ rising again after many months of no change.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The results suggest that the best models will almost always ____ both vertical and horizontal processes.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "disrupt", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Even with support, because of his health and limits on the hours he could work, he was unable to fulfill the duties of the ____ teaching job.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "intense", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "strong, extreme"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The best way to ensure that your machine has a ____ name is to use your University account name for your computer name.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "unique", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The robot will ____ medications, and alert help if the patient falls.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "\"In the modern business world, the most important ____ of leadership is the ability to create an", "Opt_1": "perspective", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most companies ____ to replace machines, like refrigerators or computers, if they break down in the first year.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Austen does not convince us that a woman with Jane's mind, integrity, emotional intensity could fall and ____ in love with such a dubious character.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "donate", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "After ____ criticism the government has decided to restore language courses for immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Princeton University computer scientist Edward Felton has decided not to ____ a paper on how his research team broke the code of copyright protection.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Madam Chair, I move that the matter under discussion is not the ____ business of the Senate.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "After the attacks of September 11, 2001, Pat Cornell turned her ____ to detecting and preventing terrorism.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "comparison", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Workers will ____ to where wages are higher.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "migrate", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It was found that only 10 of these comparisons were acceptably consistent, meaning that their inconsistency ____ exceeded 35%.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is especially important to remember that parents as a group have not usually taken the riding lessons and are not ____ to supervise their children.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although most universities say they place a high value on teaching, faculty often feel that teaching is somehow ____ to the administration.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the reasons for invading Iraq were to gain control of its oil.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was a time when priests were experiencing financial ____ and the Church was unable to subsidize many of their expenses.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A feeling prevailed that there were no rules at all on a campus that, only a few years earlier, prided itself on the implementation of ____ regulations.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school wanted to attract students from families outside the usual ____ of business and finance.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Do not write on the board with ____ ink. It cannot be erased.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government had to ____ that it had not succeeded in its plans to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The police ____ set up a committee whose task was to investigate the reasons for the shooting of the wrong man.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a reasonable request for extension of the project ____ date.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The past 20 years have seen a ____ increase in our understanding of the biology of cancer.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In the heat of election campaigning, it is in no-one's interest to ____ an artificial crisis upon the economy.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "impose", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You have received this e-mail in the ____ belief that its contents would be of interest to you.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "serious", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "severe, large", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The more alert you are to the key words used and the explicit claims made in ads, the more ____ you will become of your own use of words and ideas.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please remember to ____ any rented vehicle before driving it and note any scratches or other damage to the vehicle on the rental form.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "adjust", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this problem you have to ____ that x=7.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If the number of sections to be taught does not ____ to the number of students, you need to explain the reason.", "Opt_1": "construct", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "appeal", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to make", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people do not ____ a top engineering education with a liberal arts setting.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "disperse", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "One enjoyable way to improve in English is to do ____ of reading.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I do not ____ about your right to an opinion, but I do ____ about your inability to see the truth when it is explained to you.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Infinite ____ is so vast and incomprehensible an idea that the mind of man must necessarily be bewildered in the contemplation of it.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If your reply is not ____ at all to the subject line, start a new thread with a fresh subject line.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Despite the political, economic and cultural success of the Arab city states, Islam for many years did not spread into the ____ of East.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has not been very successful in reducing teenage drinking, but it must ____ in its efforts.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "persist", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As ____ pottery workers experimented with the effects of higher temperatures on ceramics, they began to develop methods to produce a high enough temperature that copper could be melted.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "constant", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The publishing company brought a ____ of its books to display to teachers.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I find it very difficult to ____ his bad manners.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "consider", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to think", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I ____ one thing I cannot do is review the film as I wished it had been made.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Delivery of safe and timely care is a huge ____ given the complexities of modern medicine.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "To develop a ____ approach to business, managers must utilize the strengths of their employees in assigning tasks.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The need for regulation is quite ____ today but was not apparent before the early years of the 20th century.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "At no point in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would trigger an automatic decision to offer or ____ admission.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, ____ the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to overcome it.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We must hope that her heavy involvement in the school's sporting programme will not be to the ____ of her studies.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In the face of the success of industrialization, individuals must ____ and form institutions that would be in line with this task.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A records check was unable to ____ his claim that he possessed a valid license.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "assess", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Modern computers can ____ the equivalent of many millions of pages of writing.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The business has decided to ____ a large reorganization in the attempt to increase profits.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "offer", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Both of these programs can be amended as needed to ____ a particular area of vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "All of his projects ____ the idea of flexibility within different, changing environments.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many businesses offer ____ working hours. Employees can arrive early and leave early or arrive late and leave late.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "discrete", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "separate", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is also notable that in Justice Brennan agreement he commented that the Board could not ____ books based on mere disapproval of their content.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "praise", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The business tried to ____ its employees to work harder by offering an extra day's holiday to the best salesperson.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "create", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Educational research is a useful tool for both ____ and theoretical problem solving.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "By the time they reach preschool, about 1 in 3 Odham children ____ eyeglasses for astigmatism.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In this ____ of the course, we cover less familiar territory, namely the equations of relativistic acceleration.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "proportion", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "amount; number; percentage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ of happiness will not go on increasing in anything near the same proportion as the ____ of wealth.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Doctors are advising older patients to have an injection as a ____ against influenza this winter.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Arming the Bosnian Serbs was regarded as a ____ rather than a military issue.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The administrative staff will ____ the student supervisor when a student has failed to provide required documents and other ____ation.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you want your letter to be a private communication, I usually do not ____ sending copies to other people, since they may decide to act on the matter.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This ____ is due on September 23.", "Opt_1": "trait", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "assignment", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government of Israel again stated that the attack was not ____ and that it would be investigated.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some scientists ____ that we cannot infer global warming on the basis of a just few years of hot weather.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "disturb", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt, stop from working"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Turning in work completed by other students will only ____ you when it comes to the exams.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This position is the ____ chance to learn about the many different areas of marketing and business operations in a hands-on environment.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The proposal will not ____ students of the appropriate protections to which they are entitled.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You can submit your work at any time prior to the ____ date.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of global warming is one of the more contentious ____s in science.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "issue", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The aim of the proposal is to ____ people of the liberty to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There would seem a ____ chance that the United States, working with the United Nations, will lead a worldwide religious revival.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This will be a reading lesson. Please do not ____ it by trying to talk.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "disturb", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Over the course of the period there is a steady rise in the ____ of the painter, sculptor, and architect and a growing sympathy expressed for the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "expense", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "cost", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Our preliminary surveys did not ____ between different types of questions, so we were unable to explore this issue.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you want to run this software, you will need to ____ the operating system.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I ____ you to spend part of the summer vacation reading. This is an excellent way to improve your English.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Errors in grammar and vocabulary may, but do not always, ____ with comprehensibility.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There was also no apparent record of an attempt to measure the ____ between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Any student who continues to do poor work or show a bad attitude is put on a ____. If the ____ is broken, then the student is asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "route", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer simply a health problem - it is a symptom of a greater cultural ____ that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Unilateralism may not be destroying American foreign ____ as some allege. But it does have its price.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "While I am not in favor of teaching creationism in public schools, I am also not ____ to having it presented and examined.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The lessons that ____ lunch today are cancelled for a special assembly.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "European governments strongly ____ the kidnapping of a German aid worker in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There have been ____ attempts to build an intelligent robot, but so far no-one has been successful.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "local", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "in the area where you live or work"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your reading is improving fast, but you should not ____ your writing. It is through writing that you show your teachers what you know or have understood.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "distribute", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to give out", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "His idea is simply not ____ - no one is going to pay that kind of money.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ response of the Hu Jintao government has won widespread praise, both inside and outside China.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Here is a good ____ to get paid for conducting undergraduate research at UH through its Summer Research Program.", "Opt_1": "committee", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government is planning to spend a ____ amount of money on new hospitals next year.", "Opt_1": "satisfactory", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ behind this policy is that the rights of the individuals should be respected; subjects must consent to participation in research.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He was expelled from school for a ____ attempt to cheat in the end of year exams.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This interesting site offers the student of neuroscience access to an ____ amount of information on the discipline.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If your condition is ____ and is impacting only attendance, make sure you follow up with your professors and contact the Dean of Students Office.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is some ____ that she will turn in her work on time. She's not very reliable.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The results indicated that there was a significant improvement in fluency, a ____ improvement in accuracy, but no improvement in complexity.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Global warming and polar melting ____ to raise water levels and thus flood low-lying cities.", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It will help to ____ the nuclear powers from developing more advanced and more dangerous weapons.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Do you have a ____ pencil? I forgot to bring mine.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Excellent public transportation was an important ____ in the decision to award the 2012 Olympics to London.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "But the mice did not ____ thorough cognitive testing, which requires intact mobility to navigate various mazes.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A simple and often effective means to reduce blood ____ is to reduce the volume of body fluid with a diuretic.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "pressure", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The following information has been prepared to serve as a ____ to assist you in establishing criteria for a successful teaching practice.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Please ____ the missing information before submitting the form, otherwise it will be returned to you to complete.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students are strongly recommended to seek assistance from the Student Rights Officer at their campus should they decide to ____ against exclusion.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Intelligence is just one ____ in being a successful student. You also have to show initiative and perseverance.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Ours is the only ____ that can prevent a massive loss of biological diversity.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is very little difference in the quality of learning received by distance education students and ____ students, according to a study.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government minister needed time to organize his ____ to the criticisms made about his department.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "industry", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ province of the school is the teaching of science and mathematics.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The United States is a nation pulling ____ to a degree unknown in the last 25 years.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "They must ____ their information so that it is easy for the observer to understand the historical significance of their event.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The doctor began to realize that her patient was not telling the whole ____ about what was wrong.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government failed to recognize the ____ of the public's unhappiness with the new law.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Unlike the clouds on Earth, however, many of the forms of interstellar clouds are completely ____ to the human eye.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There has been a recent ____ in language teaching towards more grammar and vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "My father's company is going to ____ our move to Germany by employing an agent to help us find a house here.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The rise in the price of oil is set to accelerate in future years due to increased ____ in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "decision", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "intention to do something, choice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Look at the ____ of your homework planner! You will have to buy a new one.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I ____ to accept the idea that man is mere flotsam and jetsam in the river of life, unable to influence the unfolding events which surround him.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Close to 30% of students did not ____ it to be cheating to lie to an instructor about having an illness or some other emergency in order to extend a work deadline.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is often necessary to revise a mathematical model several times in the course of an urban operations ____ study.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The settlers decided to ____ the settlement and sail back to Cuba.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "And finally, these estimates depend to some ____ on those proven numbers and, as we've already seen, those numbers are not very reliable.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When parents decide to send their children to a ____ -paying school, education becomes a commodity.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Weeks were needed to ____ a letter from one coast to the other. Today, in the developed world, we take it for granted that transportation is affordable.", "Opt_1": "govern", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "transmit", "Opt_1_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In this section of the course, we cover less familiar territory, ____ the equations of relativistic acceleration.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The instructor is expected to ____ his or her grading policy at the beginning of the course.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "approve", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to agree to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "People have been trying for decades or maybe even centuries in an attempt to bring this ____ problem to an end.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Plagiarism is easy to ____ but often hard to define. This is partly because the legal rules differ sharply from the ethical ones.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "commit", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This report summarizes our ____ findings.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was a time when priests were experiencing financial crisis and the Church was unable to ____ many of their expenses.", "Opt_1": "strive", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In order to get people to change unhealthy habits, the government needs to use a ____ of the carrot and the stick.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students will learn to appreciate what epidemiologists mean when they say that an exposure and an ____ are associated.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most children take a ____ of domestic duties such as washing the dishes.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You will not have to seek permission to ____ if the purpose of your work falls under one of the following criteria.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is common knowledge that credit cards are a temporary solution that can snowball into a ____ problem.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The siting and design are a ____ characteristic of ancient buildings that belong to a self-enclosed precinct.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I cannot think of any ____ writers who are better than her.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In closing, I want to ____ that I know that our community is up to meeting these challenges and I know that the bold and inspiring decisions that will be made.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You should ____ the office to see if you can get aid.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He also responded that his particular school did not ____ courses in English as a Second Language (ESL).", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There are one or two ____ spelling problems but in general this is an excellent piece of writing.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "verbal", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Politicians realize that they can't know everything, so they surround themselves with people who can ____ them.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Coca-Cola is a drink that is ____ popular.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is English expression which claims: All roads lead to Rome. This means that there is more than one ____ to fame and success in life.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "proportion", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "amount; number; percentage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The two scholars are impressed with the ____ audience of readers their blog drew after their first three postings on Dec. 5, 2004.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school can recommend that parents communicate by email, but they cannot ____ on it.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There was also no ____ record of an attempt to measure the relationship between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Don't forget to ____ your research sources at the end of your writing.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Lispeth took to Christianity readily, and did not ____ it when she reached womanhood.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We view his behavior as very serious and we hope this ban will serve as an example.If you ____ the rules about downloading internet files, you will not be allowed to use the computer lab.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "adopt", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She says she's not a very good pianist, but I know that the ____ is true and she's just being modest.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The producer of these webpages has long been an ____ of the value of computers in language teaching.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government should not ____ its tax policies on what newspaper editors tell it to do.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We have found that students are more likely to complete a community health project if they ____ a team.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is research that could ____ help in the treatment of certain kinds of cancer.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I don't think she realises the ____ of the task she has set herself.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A major problem for most western societies is how to ____ immigrants with different cultures and religious beliefs.", "Opt_1": "provide", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to give", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school will ____ a new floor in the sport hall over the summer vacation.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "recover", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to get back"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "My guess is that it had no ____ on prices except, possibly, the very first time, and that this ____ would probably have been very minor.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Sitting too long in front of a computer may ____ headaches or back problems.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "stimulate", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "My overall ____ of him since he joined the class is very positive.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We can only suppose that Fulton was already too deeply committed to his ____ plan to consider alternative ideas.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "overlap", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The cost of gas (petrol) will continue to ____ as the price of oil goes up or down.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "fluctuate", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to vary; to rise and fall"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If someone invites you to their party, it's polite to send them a ____ and tell them if you can come or not.", "Opt_1": "benefit", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company's ____ in the second half of the year is to increase its export business.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Yet Bush also has adopted other, more ____ policy positions on guns and gun control.", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you look at the course policies you will ____ an item that accounts for 4% of your grade.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Vehicles that do not ____ a valid parking permit will be towed immediately.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Our focus is to ____ each student to achieve their full potential as they strive for success in our five cornerstones of Academic Excellence.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A verbal contract is impossible to prove, and the organization will always ____ that it was a misunderstanding.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "distribute", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to give out", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company report did not do much to illuminate the reasons for the fall in business in the ____ year.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "That doesn't mean I have a personality disorder because I ____ myself in a different manner to different people.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "DeRosa's success is a genuine example of how the right ____ and excellent faculty really can cause a scholarly transformation.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He is ____ considered a pioneer in this field, both in conducting research and in educating students to assume key positions in industry.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The current program review process is not very ____ because there are neither rewards nor punishments for outcomes.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "spontaneous", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "happening without warning or planning"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school wanted to attract students from families outside the usual ____ of business and finance.", "Opt_1": "sphere", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There was a ____ demonstration on the streets of London to protest the government's plans to go to war in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "massive", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you ____ the stairs by the nurse's office, you will see the cafeteria in front of you.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We have never in history needed to ____ of so much waste as we do today.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The best way to ensure that your machine has a unique name is to use your University ____ name for your computer name.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ danger to the soldiers is suicide bombers at the checkpoints.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Vegetable crops are the most important ____ group for small farms in southern states and their importance is expected to increase.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "guide", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Over the course of her journey in the program she has come a great ____ from her primary focus as an agent for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Respect is not a commodity. You have to ____ it; you cannot buy it.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government must ____ to make every effort to prevent young people from becoming addicted to drugs.", "Opt_1": "resist", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to fight against", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Each student's experience was so varied that I was unable to ____ common themes for discussion.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In response to these events, this study was initiated to define and investigate the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In sports events it is a good idea at the start of the game to ____ energy that you are going to need later.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "attend", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to ____ a limit on the number of solutions searched for, since in general the number of such solutions could be infinite.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "impose", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ trade agreements have failed to include meaningful, enforceable labour or environmental standards.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You can lessen your risk of getting a cold in the winter if you ____ others who already have one!", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "warn", "Opt_3": "avoid", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Not all ESL students know that the subject PE ____ physical exercise.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A verbal contract is impossible to prove, and the organization will always ____ that it was a misunderstanding.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In most school parents are asked to ____ to their child participating in sex education lessons.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "How can educators design ____ to maximize the learning of all students?", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government of Israel again stated that the attack was not ____ and that it would be investigated.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "significant", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "No wonder your computer doesn't work. You must ____ it to the monitor!", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He mentioned what seemed like a huge sum. It was ____ a huge amount for a programme that had only a skeleton staff and strained budget.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many of the students were unable to ____ the relevance of the mathematics they had learned and so could not make use of it.", "Opt_1": "consist", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Learning lots of academic words will ____ your chances of success in school.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ the way that animals are used in medical experiments.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Should the counselor attempt to identify him and inform him that there is a ____ to his future children?", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We must ____ and strengthen existing laws and institute new procedures aimed at terrorists and criminals.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Scientists have found life over a mile below the ____ of the sea, far from the sun.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She is no ____ student. She can speak 5 languages and play the piano to a very high standard.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Today women and men have the same ____ in western society. This wasn't always the case.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "status", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The USA is designing a spaceship that will land on Mars and ____ its polar regions.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The demonstrators failed to interrupt the ____ of the Olympic torch through the city streets.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "European governments strongly ____ the kidnapping of a German aid worker in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "interrupt", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is important to ____ that the information noted on the sign-off form is correct and that all necessary signatures have been obtained.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Mechanisms by which comfrey can ____ the liver are unclear, but the main injury appears to be destruction of small veins, leading to cirrhosis.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "descend", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to go down"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It only drew more ____ to the 13-year-old Robertson panel report and the CIA's role in the investigation of UFOs.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Photoshop provides you with techniques used to ____ the quality of graphics and photographs.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "terminate", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most western countries want to ____ with China. It's the largest market in the world and its developing fast.", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "examine", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the ____ of the program but prior language study is not a criterion for selection.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I don't think the government will manage to ____ many people to recycle more of their garbage.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Traditional social skills strategies (such as board games about friendships and ____ classroom behavior) tend to be too subtle for many children.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This was not ____ of Serbia alone; the population felt similar frustration in other parts of Yugoslavia and in Eastern Europe.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Earth's ____ is divided into four layers, which is typical of rocky planets.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Selecting the panelists is no easy task, and is subject to ____ lobbying.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "vague", "Answer": "intense", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "They still ____ copying the work from the internet, but I ran a Google search and found it immediately.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The plants in many of the world's ____ places have not yet been analysed for their possible medical effects.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Studies have proven that taste is only a minor consideration in the ____ decision for soft drinks.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I think Kerry's biggest error, as a politician, is that he failed to ____ himself from Bush in any meaningful way.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She had shown no propensity to ____ in abusive conduct.", "Opt_1": "coordinate", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "suggest", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school had to pay a small ____ to the parents of the boy who hurt his arm on the ski trip.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A ____ to save life has recently been waged at the Kwangtze Hospital in Shanghai. This ____ is not yet over, but it has already caused a great sensation.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "guarantee", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is ____ important that you don't miss the deadline.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Until 30 years ago, this was not a ____ problem because most could work in the agricultural and industrial economies of the day with little education.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "unique", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Scientists don't know how to predict drought a month or more in ____ for most locations.", "Opt_1": "recommend", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What skills did you ____ in the process of completing your course?", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "attain", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ problem facing the world this century is how to reduce global warming.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of this unit is to teach students how a seemingly unimportant event can have a significant effect on their lives.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We will continue to see new immigrants coming to our city, and we will need to ____ their access into the medical care system.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "After ____ criticism the government has decided to restore language courses for immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is a ____ of toilets in the school. Every time I want to use one, it is occupied.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Do we have an ____ to help the poor?", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The many hours of practice that usually ____ exceptional performance remain out of sight to the casual observer.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "enhance", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to make something better"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of blue agave (agave azul) cactus in Mexico has gone from one extreme to another during the past several years.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Her ____ was that the Korean people believe that the U.S. policy is to have a divided Korea and that the U.S. is the reason the two countries are not united.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I MUST see the headmaster at once! It's ____ !", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You need to know a little more about the background before you ____ the government's decision.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "accompany", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer simply a health problem - it is a ____ of a greater cultural shift that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Whereas the origin of galactic magnetic fields has long posed a challenge for astrophysicists to explain, they ____ feel that they can say where they were not formed.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You ____ yourself to unnecessary danger if you drive a car without wearing a seat belt.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "commence", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to start", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government must be prepared for an attack from people who ____ its decision.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He may ____ to any political party he pleases, or he may ____ to none.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "belong", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is ____ the scope of this course.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He did not get a ____ response to his request for a day's absence from work.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Whereas the origin of galactic magnetic fields has long posed a challenge for astrophysicists to explain, they ____ feel that they can say where they were not formed.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has made ____ any progress towards reducing environmental pollution.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After Iraq some people feel strongly that the USA should never again ____ in the affairs of other countries.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If children of seven years and older will be included in the study, an ____ agreement is necessary.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some people ____ the USA of starting the war in Iraq in order to gain control of its oilfields.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The essential ____ for successful teaching is the ability to interest the students.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of the government's willingness to pay kidnappers to release hostages is that now there are more kidnappings and more hostages.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I cannot think of any ____ writers who are better than her.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some families who emigrate to Germany are surprised at the ____ of sweeping the street in front of your house every Saturday morning.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Columbus did not ____ slavery to the New World; the practice existed there before his arrival.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Richards understood the importance of her position, the image that she projected and the need to ____ her papers and records at the Center.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A student who fails to cite sources in a ____ attempt to conceal the source of the work should be considered to be cheating.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In a world of infinite problems but finite resources, competition for adequate ____ and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "asset", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "impulse", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It seems probable that precise measurements of the ratio of ____ to negative responses will help to decide between the several processes.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "optional", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The two parties paid for these mistakes through ____ poor performance in the final national elections.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Though Sima and Codreanu both attempted to prevent the murder, it ____ took place, and produced harsh consequences.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was a chance to try out something different and immerse myself completely in another culture and it was a ____ I did not regret.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "choice", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "decision, selection"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The instructor is expected to announce his or her grading ____ at the beginning of the course.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government must not hesitate in taking harsh actions ____ communism and all its supporters.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to ____ your instinct as to whether he is the right man to marry.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school will ____ its new vacation sports and study program at the beginning of next month.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "launch", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The assessment was not independent of influence by Coca-Cola (i.e. the final report appeared to have been edited by Coca-Cola ____ to its release.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Farmers ____ their crops. This means that they do not grow the same thing on the same field for more than one year.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "raise", "Answer": "rotate", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to lift; to make higher"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He both provided a message service and the ____ needed to send and receive wireless messages.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Computer scan technology can enhance the ____ of many sports injuries.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We know it's not 100% correct, but it's the best ____ that we can produce at this time.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "number"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She claimed, furthermore, that the item did not acknowledge the positive developments in the ____ since the turn of the century.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government failed to recognize the ____ of the public's unhappiness with the new law.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "dimension", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "importance; amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The first principle of this school is that all nationalities and cultures are equally important, even if some are more represented than others ____ the body of students.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In a world of infinite problems but finite resources, competition for ____ attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The outcome of the government's willingness to pay kidnappers to ____ hostages is that now there are more kidnappings and more hostages.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "release", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What motives have thus incited him to ____ all the hardships and temptations he encountered on his way from a miserable life to an honorable one.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The developing world does not create many industrial wastes; thus it has had little opportunity to develop ____ disposal techniques.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "formal", "Opt_3": "proper", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_3_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government decided to increase its ____ to the countries of eastern Africa.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "For republicans since Cicero there can be no liberty without law, and no valid law or ____ system when liberty is disregarded.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The purpose of this study was to explore the internal and ____ factors influencing the career development of first generation Filipina Americans.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ put forward in this paper depends in no degree upon the completeness of our knowledge of the former condition of the organic world.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Revenue from ____ tax is expected to be lower this year than in previous years.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He seems to be lacking the impulse to improve his ____ poor grades.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Mississippi is a ____ river.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "legitimate", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "correct; allowed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Toscano, professor of history, talks about the war but refuses to let it ____ his curriculum.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "interrupt", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The precise answer is not at all straightforward, unless the uncertainty itself is ____ in a particular way to the passage of time.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She very ____ comes late to class. I hope there is nothing wrong.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The first ____ on the agenda is the proposal to increase working hours to 42 per work.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This illustrates the variety of rational choices that a criminal would make in the ____ to commit a crime.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Too much stress can trigger problems with mental and physical health, particularly over a prolonged ____ of time.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The number of ____ warm nights and the length of heat waves will increase significantly over nearly all land areas across the globe.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school does not own the sports hall. It belongs to the ____ council, which charges the school to use it.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Due to the new law, smokers will now have to ____ the pleasure of a cigarette with their drink in a restaurant or bar.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The water ____ is one of the natural processes that are familiar to most students.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All political parties must ____ in their proposals to stamp out racism.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Remember that more than one factor may be the cause of a problem and that symptoms may often ____ in their appearance.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "overlap", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Al Gore ____ did not deserve the Nobel peace prize. On a personal level, he has not reduced his own carbon dioxide emissions.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many people are very concerned about the new identity card system that the government plans to ____ at great expense.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you come from an EU country and follow a study programme in the Netherlands, you may be eligible for a ____ for these tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The management is considering removing the salesmen's ____ to use company cars at the weekend for private purposes.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ language of the school is English but many documents are also translated into German.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is no trace of an ____ idea in this essay.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government promised to review its ____ on drug criminality.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Mr. Elliott was at fault for delegating that function to a person who lacked the ____ to perform the job properly.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You are advised to ____ serious language study both before and during the course of the program but prior language study is not a criterion for selection.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All students must ____ at the beginning of the school year that they understand and will follow the plagiarism policy.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Can I come and see you after school today? I would like to ____ my math project.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The decision to make cannabis legal in small amounts is a significant ____ in the government's policy.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The teacher should vary presentation styles and take into account ____ abilities and interests.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Therefore, it is important to ____ low birth weight infants according to their weight for their gestational age.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is only one error in your writing. You put: He play tennis ____ of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It's not easy to ____ yourself when you're not going out and actually preparing for an opponent.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The best remedy is to change the nutrient solution every week ____ of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some people believe that harsh prison penalties for young criminals ____ natural justice.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "offend", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to go against; to upset"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "When the models incorporate the effects of pollution, they predict that rainfall will ____ even more in the next few decades.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Our very ____ makes us aware of our need to do the utmost toward improving the situation of our not-so-fortunate neighbors.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "profession", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "job; occupation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There was little ____ that the government's plans to increase taxes would be very unpopular.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A student who fails to cite sources in a ____ attempt to conceal the source of the work should be considered to be cheating.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "hostile", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Too much ____ can trigger problems with mental and physical health, particularly over a prolonged period of time.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the administration failed to ____ its responsibility to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "One study found that anemia was a strong predictor of other serious problems that were not ____ at the time anemia was first detected.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further ____ of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is a truism that death - not just our own - affects all of us, even if it is a ____ most people do not want to contemplate for long.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "These two-word verbs ____ one other problem, besides not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He said several times that money was not a ____ in the decision, and it was not about safety alone.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was the result of his labour that Brazil could ____ scientific institutions.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is very little ____ of the poor and middle class as our corrupt judges have developed a system called lawyer denial.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Microsoft has promised that the ____ operating system will be more secure than ever before.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "forthcoming", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The profession of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and ____ of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is not a ____ in the notion of economic development as much as it is a problem with the fiscal structure of Alaska.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In other words, his father did not invest the ____ of resources, whether they be human or monetary, necessary for success.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This line on the playground is the ____ to where you are allowed to go as a grade 7 student.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Men and women of all ages benefit from a ____ amount of daily physical activity (for example: 30 minutes of brisk walking or 15 minutes of jogging).", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "certain", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "sure", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You must turn in the ____ by next Friday. There can be no delay.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "assignment", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has increased the tax on petrol, ____ making itself very unpopular with motorists.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Although the agreement was compulsory ____ than voluntary, it led to substantial military reforms along French lines.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The media and the public should not blame the music ____ for the jobs that parents are not fulfilling.", "Opt_1": "asset", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Photoshop provides you with techniques used to ____ the quality of graphics and photographs.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Dinosaurs no longer ____ - they have been extinct for millions of years.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Princeton University computer scientist Edward Felton has decided not to publish a paper on how his research team broke the ____ of copyright protection.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The US government is considering if it should ____ its army from Iraq.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Obviously the result of many years of reading and reflection, this ____ study contains detailed summaries of dozens of works, both major and minor.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "To remain eligible for financial aid, recipients are required to show satisfactory progress toward a ____ according to the guidelines listed below.", "Opt_1": "concept", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As long as the person did not ____ large amounts of protein and carbohydrates, the effect on fat digestion was negated.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "consume", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to ____ the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are worth it!", "Opt_1": "signify", "Opt_2": "import", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is no place for those who have failed to ____ to better themselves with the opportunity afforded them.", "Opt_1": "strive", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The journey to peace and prosperity in the region can only ____ when the civic authority is brought back in.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "commence", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to start", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The fat cells that surround coronary arteries may play a central and previously unrecognized ____ in the development of cardiovascular disease.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "role", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "job or function", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We need to put our minds together and decide if we need to collaborate ____ our institutions to provide a new service.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of child deaths in the nineteenth century is one which could hardly fail to interest any serious scholar of the period.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We got some very ____ results in our science experiment. I think the thermometer was not working correctly.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "poor", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government's proposals will have a profound ____ on the education of every child in the country.", "Opt_1": "principle", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "rule", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "They simply decided for various reasons that his age was not a drawback, that ____ (at that time and for that position) it was an advantage.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "After massive criticism the government has decided to ____ language courses for immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "My family can't ____ a new house. They're so expensive in Germany.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government is going to introduce a law that will ____ smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A ____ problem is that many companies will only employ workers with experience, but how do young people gain that experience if they are not given a job. This is called a \"vicious circle\".", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Fully 10 percent of the U.S. population has some ____ of learning disability; the true figure may in fact be higher.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teacher did not ____ that one of the students had been crying for most of the lesson.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government was unable to ____ that it was considering invading North Korea.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Every 10 years the government carries out a ____ survey of all households in the country. This is called a census.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Production of oil and gas will ____ unless new reserves of oil and gas are discovered and developed.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The text should contain a ____ description of the aims and scope of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The main objective of the proposed research is to investigate the ____ of West African languages.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many stores have special offers to ____ new customers.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "My ESL teacher has the ____ to talk about his own school days.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "To include an image on your website, you will need to ____ the image into your webpage using an HTML editor.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is never too late to ____ healthy habits! American Institute for Cancer Research.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We ____ outside counsel to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ student at our school spends about 90 minutes doing homework every evening.", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The plants in many of the world's ____ places have not yet been analysed for their possible medical effects.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Working with the Teacher Assistant is not ____ but recommended.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Knowing when to ____ treatment for mental health disorders is important for parents and families.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "seek", "Answer": "seek", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to look for or want"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has announced ____ plans to reduce long-term unemployment.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I'm sorry, but I will ____ not be able to come to the meeting next week.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is ____ that you hand in the essay on time. If you don't, you will fail the course.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The conclusion did not distort the ____ of the situation even though the student distorted some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The lack of available parking spaces is a significant ____ to faculty and students.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Above all, a teacher must be firm when dealing with requests for grade changes and other ____ matters.", "Opt_1": "related", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is often ____ to associate a complex set of \"metadata\" with each data point in order to make that datum useful.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "necessary", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Eat less, exercise more: the ____ for weight loss is so simple, yet so hard.", "Opt_1": "formula", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "impulse", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Do you think I will pass the test? - It will ____ how hard you work from now until the day of the examination.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students who take the class are expected to choose a contemporary problem they would like to address and ____ with each other in researching it.", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "However, no one ____ will be the sole reason for lack of admission to the program.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "stage", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Sometimes it is difficult to find the exact word to ____ an idea. This is particularly true if you are speaking in your second language.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "An even number multiplied by an ____ number will always yield an even number.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Scientists don't know how to predict drought a month or more in ____ for most locations.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "advance", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government is thinking of passing a law that will require all house owners to ____ their oil heating system for one that runs on gas.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Why did the Bush Administration ____ to modify its goals in order to achieve a consensus?", "Opt_1": "refuse", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "commence", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to start", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If we ____ your request to amend the information, we will make reasonable efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "expose", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As the earthquake waves travel, they ____ all of the principles of other types of wave motion.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We would probably become engaged in discussions from which we could not extract ourselves and ____ our freedom of action would be limited.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He was expelled from school for a ____ attempt to cheat in the end of year exams.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many people buy supplementary vitamin pills because they do not believe that they get enough vitamins from their ____ food.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Your grades will continue to ____ unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "fare", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ocean floor is the last great ____ waiting to be exploited for its oil and other minerals.", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is still too soon to say whether the invasion of Iraq was ____ it.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Why, Graeme Newman asks, has reform after reform failed to halt the ____ of crime?", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "spread", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Our focus is to motivate each student to achieve their full ____ as they strive for success in our five cornerstones of Academic Excellence.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government clearly did not ____ carefully enough on the consequences of its new law.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To develop a comprehensive approach to business, managers must ____ the strengths of their employees in assigning tasks.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The practice test materials will become available just ____ to the class.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The man had been reported to the police because of his ____ behaviour over the last few days. He was now under observation.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "But when planned and ____ policy forces the price of oil down without good commercial reasons, then that means another war against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally rigid bodies ____ multiple, concurrent, dynamic frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The police need to ____ more evidence before they can make any arrests.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The publishing company brought a ____ of its books to display to teachers.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "After ____ years of work, the project team was not able to gather the political support needed to maintain funding for the integrated service program.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The unit did not cover nuclear weapons in as much ____ as some of my students would have liked.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Both Initial and Wokingham now dispute the ____ for the cost of food and say it is lower.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you accept a housing assignment in the Summer Allocation and subsequently ____ it or fail to move in, you are charged an administrative fee.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "cancel", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We view his behavior as very serious and we hope this ____ will serve as an example.If you violate the rules about downloading internet files, you will not be allowed to use the computer lab.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "ban", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Infinite ____ is so vast and incomprehensible an idea that the mind of man must necessarily be bewildered in the contemplation of it.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Actually if two ____ tones of the same frequency and intensity are produced simultaneously, they will combine.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Bulgaria is to face a ____ shortage of teachers within the next three years, education experts declared.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "severe", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Mrs Cho spoke on ____ of the Korean Parents Group and thanked the school for buying Korean books for the library.", "Opt_1": "experience", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The late bus will ____ at 5:30 today, not at 5:15 as usual.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "depart", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The U.S. government likely approached China on this matter prior to the announcement of sanctions, but did not receive a ____ response.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "odd", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "strange, unusual"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For my next step I would propose to the students ____ distinctions that might at first glance seem to be completely arbitrary or valueless.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We could not ____ any significant effect of our dietary recommendations in terms of birth weight and duration of pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "detect", "Opt_2": "implement", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_2_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Oddly, however, the book is almost completely ____ in fictional representations of invalids.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She very ____ comes late to class. I hope there is nothing wrong.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In the face of the success of industrialization, individuals must ____ and form institutions that would be in line with this task.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "unite", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly rigid ____ of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When morality comes up against ____, it is seldom ____ that loses.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government plans to raise the money they ____ to poor countries in the Third World.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "donate", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He mentioned what seemed like a huge sum. It was indeed a huge amount for a ____ that had only a skeleton staff and strained budget.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "With her ____ it is not surprising that she has had problems in her new school.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A ____ error in editing is to fix a word or phrase at one part of a sentence and not see that the fix affected something else in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Hundreds of people gathered outside Parliament to ____ about the government's decision to raise the tax on cigarettes.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "ensure", "Opt_4": "fear", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_4_def": "to be concerned or frightened about"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I asked for a concise ____ of what happened. So why have you given me a 20-page report?", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "response", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "answer or reply; reaction"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many people think that the government's proposals to ____ teenage crime are superficial and will not work.", "Opt_1": "signify", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "reduce", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The two procedures consistently showed that garlic did not inhibit the ____ of oral bacteria.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ assumes a single step - that life originated on Earth - ahead of the more elaborate idea that life formed elsewhere and was subsequently transported to Earth.", "Opt_1": "rigid", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There was a ____ in the cafeteria at lunch today. The oil for cooking French fries ignited and set fire to the wooden ceiling.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We southerners, and ____ we white southerners, owe a huge debt to valiant civil rights leaders like Martin Luther King.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is often impossible to ____ the pronunciation of a word from its spelling alone.", "Opt_1": "reject", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "undertake", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will analyze recurrent patterns of international political conflict, identify underlying issues, and suggest ____ resolutions.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "After an ____ period of introduction and practice, the German course begins with Chapter 1 in the text Deutsch: Na klar!", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Iraqi regime failed to take that ____ opportunity to cooperate with the United Nations investigation.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "verbal", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This section is not an alternative to reading course materials or attending lectures, but rather an opportunity ____ topics in greater detail.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "encounter", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a diverse ____ society will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "global", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "world", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Institute itself was an ____ separate from the Chemistry department.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "lecture", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She has no ____ of studying in peace at home. Her domestic life is too chaotic.", "Opt_1": "committee", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "After about a year his family realized that this was not just a ____ and that he was serious about me and that we really cared about each other.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He was also faced with difficult questions about the university's handling of the emergency and whether it did enough to ____ students.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Not everyone is ____ enough to have internet access at home.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "fortunate", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If men and women do equivalent jobs they should ____ equivalent pay.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "compel", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If the human body is weak or cold, it is less able to ____ infection.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ how the government can hope to win the forthcoming election.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "entitle", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to give the right to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Turning in work completed by other students will only ____ you when it comes to the exams.", "Opt_1": "destroy", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is no ____ of him passing the course. He has been away too many times this year.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A student who is in ____ to the University at the end of any academic term shall not be permitted to register in the University again.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "debt", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you currently do not ____ the skill to meet this standard, you are advised to enroll in a class that will provide you with this capability.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is a ____ at our school to have a pizza party for the new students.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ sector of the UK economy is much more successful than the manufacturing sector.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Did anyone manage to ____ question 11?", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It offers an effective solution to a problem based on good audience analysis, and fulfills ____ as well as all major purposes.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has banned smoking in virtually all ____ places.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to control to avoid an ____ answer.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students must have ____ to a PC that has at least a 700 MHz processor.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "What is absent in your essay is any reference to the ____ of your ideas.", "Opt_1": "argument", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In proof of this, we may note that slavery did not ____ immediately on the reception of Christianity.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "yield", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to produce", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "As a general rule, all persons wishing to ____ the conference must register and pay for participation.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to impose a ____ on the number of solutions searched for, since in general the number of such solutions could be infinite.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This book has much ____ text that will make it difficult for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "temporary", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She would have a better chance of academic success if she didn't ____ in so many activities outside of school.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Institute must take greater measures to ____ students that they need not fear consequences when seeking medical help for substance abuse.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Radio and TV stations often ____ for money from their audience in order to help people suffering from disasters.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Tobacco smoke was a ____ of life up through the 1970s.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A group of artists who were working and teaching in the Boston area had a bold idea: to create a new kind of school for professional education in the ____ arts.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but ____ language study is not a criterion for selection.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ resulted from the fact that the Jews agreed to the resolution but the local Arabs refused to acknowledge the Israeli State.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "History is filled with examples of military leaders who have suffered at the mercy of climate conditions that they failed to ____ adequately.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "contemplate", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In general, when you paraphrase, you use about the same number of words to ____ the idea that the writer uses in the text.", "Opt_1": "regard", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The University of Washington has agreed to ____ a class-action lawsuit over faculty salaries.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you want to do well in tests then you will need to reduce the ____ of time watching TV and spend more time studying.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some students ____ to go to the bathroom when in fact all they want to do is escape a boring lesson for a few minutes.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, thus is unable to ____ insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Workers will ____ to where wages are higher.", "Opt_1": "manifest", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "migrate", "Opt_1_def": "show", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This was not ____ of Serbia alone; the population felt similar frustration in other parts of Yugoslavia and in Eastern Europe.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The writer Emile Zola exposed the ____ to the general public in the literary newspaper L'Aurore (The Dawn) in a famous open letter to the President.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "affair", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "affair", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is a ____ belief that scaling up HIV voluntary counseling and testing (VCT) programs in Africa will have large prevention benefits.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "arbitrary", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teacher spoke so fast that it was difficult to ____ all the information he was giving.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "absorb", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to take up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For the purposes of this study, then, increasing the testing strength did not ____ more accurate results.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company was unable to ____ its recent good trade figures.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was an ____ idea to allow the students to write their own test.", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I don't believe you made a ____ effort to improve. Your grades certainly have not got better.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Why, Graeme Newman asks, has reform after reform failed to halt the ____ of crime?", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "spread", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The new legislation will ____ all immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Due to the ____ shortage of highly trained nursing staff, Hopkins was unable to assemble a full team of qualified personnel.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "severe", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Is the Smartboard just the latest teaching ____ that will be popular for a year or so and then disappear without trace?", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is research that could eventually help in the ____ of certain kinds of cancer.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to promote the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are ____ it!", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A major factor in our ____ is how long it will take.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This alone makes the book a worthwhile read for students whose received knowledge about Africans is often little more than a stereotype of ____ victims.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "passive", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This course list should ____ the number of credits and the grade option (grade, pass/fail, audit) for each enrolled student.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The unexpected shortage of flu vaccine during winter 2004/2005 caused ____ concern.", "Opt_1": "comprehensive", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "full, complete", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Click for information about ____ drinking ages in the United States and around the world.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some information is collected on our ____ by outside agencies in order to provide services to our visitors.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some people ____ poor immigrants - employing them as house cleaners for very low pay.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "assess", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students with Advanced Placement scores of 4 or 5 in English Language ____ a credit toward graduation but not toward the English major.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You need to ____ the material covered by the homework problems in order to pass the quizzes and final examination.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The fact that speech is likely to ____ in some violence or in destruction of property is not enough to justify its suppression.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "disaster", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "a huge problem or failure"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to first exhaust all possibilities for Federal and state financial aid programs before seeking ____ loans.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school established a ____ to discuss the introduction of a bilingual programme.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Fish farming is an ____ that should go some way to compensating for the reduction of fish in the oceans.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The teacher thought about the best opportunity to ____ that she was leaving to have a baby.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My ____ intention was to resign, but then I changed my mind.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The first section of this course is concerned with understanding the ____ concepts of design: How to analyze and talk about visual material.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "basic", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "first or easy", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Thousands of farm families are being forced off the land, and we are being told that it is an ____ consequence of technological progress.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The unpleasant ____ in the computer lab is sure to occupy my thoughts in the next few days.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "What steps do I take to draw a ____ sample of a target audience in my county to do a needs assessment or gather baseline data?", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "random", "Answer": "random", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "by chance; without any sequence"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Assign students to groups; ____ rules for participation, and rotate jobs within each group.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I think the students enjoy the fact that they have the ____ to try different things, says Harris. You can ask them to expand and see which direction they take.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school is working on a ____ to give all students a portable computer for use in lessons.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The causes of gun and knife crime ____ young people is an important field of inquiry.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The teacher left an ____ that no homework was to be set in her absence.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Eat less, ____ more: the formula for weight loss is so simple, yet so hard.", "Opt_1": "sample", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She was raised by a family that did not appreciate the significance of racial differences and the importance of developing a ____ racial identity.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "subjective", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These findings suggest that something in the brain's pain-processing and pain-killing systems may ____ by race and ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "resource", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We recognize that ____ beyond a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "phase", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most companies ____ to replace machines, like refrigerators or computers, if they break down in the first year.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "____ times for farming can also mean tough times for marriages.", "Opt_1": "Subsequent", "Opt_2": "Tough", "Opt_3": "Uniform", "Opt_4": "Invisible", "Answer": "Tough", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I ____ one thing I cannot do is review the film as I wished it had been made.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "identify", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A group of artists who were working and teaching in the Boston area had a ____ idea: to create a new kind of school for professional education in the visual arts.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The text should contain a concise description of the aims and ____ of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "pressure", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I am ____ surprised I did so well in the test because I didn't work very hard this term.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "With noise levels of this magnitude, hearing damage is a ____ problem unless some sort of hearing protection is used.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "distinct", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The student's answer may not address all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or ____ analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In each classroom of the school there are 3 recycling bins. This is a small way to help ____ the environment.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many people believe that the government will not ____ with its plans to decriminalize cannabis.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "undertake", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "His examination failure did not ____ through lack of effort or ability but because of serious illness in the weeks before.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Because of the increase in the price of oil the company was unable to ____ to its plans to employ new workers.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "adhere", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You are making ____ progress in learning English.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is surprising what you can ____ if you make an effort.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It's difficult to ____ why he made such a foolish decision.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "attend", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school have employed some guards to make the campus more secure ____ unannounced visitors.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Another significant ____ was provided by the results of the post-hoc test of Recognition Motivation.", "Opt_1": "asset", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the growth of the internet has been to the detriment of students' ability and willingness to read.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The internet allows people to ____ whatever they want without needing to go to the shops.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "procure", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In this section of the course, we cover less familiar territory, ____ the equations of relativistic acceleration.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of your writing is not at all clear to me.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The public are ____ satisfied with the government's performance.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Unfortunately, many drug users emerge from prison only to find themselves back there a few months later. This is because they cannot find or keep a job, and need to steal to ____ their drug-taking habits.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This form is to be used by students who ____ to add or drop a course during the first two weeks of the trimester.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "seek", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The sorting of students into homogeneous ability and achievement groups is nearly as old as universal ____ education in the United States.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most of the school's ____ comes from the school fees paid by the companies who send their employees to work in Germany.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They all use tools from well outside the natural ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The decision on whether to shut down its nuclear power stations is among the most ____ issues facing the government.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There seemed to be no ____ of coping with the war debts that were overwhelming both nation and states.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The study of Growth and Development can help us to know a person more thoroughly and ____ be better doctors.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In this paper we describe simple identification and signature schemes which ____ any user to prove his identity and the authenticity of his messages.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students arriving late had ____ failed to read the reminder post card.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I prefer to believe that the quality of my thinking has not diminished; I simply have chosen a different ____ to express my ideas.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "affair", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "format", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The management wanted to dismiss the incompetent employee but could find no-one better to ____ him.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "risk", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Richards understood the importance of her position, the image that she projected and the need to ____ her papers and records at the Center.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Next you need to ____ a search statement so you can conduct a database search.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is common knowledge that ____ cards are a temporary solution that can snowball into a permanent problem.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Computers are a much more ____ way of storing and retrieving large amounts of data than keeping it on paper in huge cabinets.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian ____ have in common besides being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school's ____ have been improved recently with the addition of a second library and media centre.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He reminds us that ____ teaching methods are part of coming of age in the world of the Japanese performing arts.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "harsh", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Questioning the values of parents is ____ in being a teenager.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The UCLA Philharmonia, however, is bridging the gap between North and South campuses with two concerts that ____ symphony with science and history.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "launch", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to begin", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "At no point in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would trigger an ____ decision to offer or deny admission.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Individual academies ____ the curriculum in the manner that best fits local facilities and opportunities.", "Opt_1": "highlight", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We need to regulate ____ to new lands made possible by road expansion.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A common teacher ____ to students who are not listening in class is: Pay attention.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She stopped smoking and started exercising. As a ____ her health improved considerably.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ between the workers and the management improved when flexible working time was introduced.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The best ____ is to change the nutrient solution every week instead of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "remedy", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "cure (often for an illness)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The meeting will ____ at 8.30.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It offers an ____ solution to a problem based on good audience analysis, and fulfills minor as well as all major purposes.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "arbitrary", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many students doing an important test try to ____ their answers with their hand or a book. They don't want their neighbour seeing what they have written.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School has attracted many more German students recently. My ____ is that parents are not happy with the education their children are getting in German public schools.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Collecting information with no particular plan or purpose and then hoping to ____ it into a research project is not likely to succeed.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some people say that there should be ____ schools for students who are not so interested in writing or learning from books.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The drugs are used to enhance ____ artificially to the degree that they give athletes a competitive edge.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "However, his proposal contains a ____ that is important to recognize and understand.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "custom", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "To accommodate the great power ____ now rapidly occurring in Asia, the United States needs vigorous preparation by its executive branch and Congress.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "shift", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "change", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Teachers often ____ student grammar errors with a yellow marker pen.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many Western businesses are finding it difficult to ____ with Asian companies which pay their workers far less money.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Research shows that earnings ____ strongly with IQ levels.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "govern", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Two thousand years from now, an archaeologist will find little ____ of the millions of web pages that have been updated in the last hour.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The two teams are ____ equal. It's difficult to predict who is going to win.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In 1996, ____ 805 million Smart cards were issued, with an estimated 2.8 billion to be distributed in 2000.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Each student's experience was so varied that I was unable to ____ common themes for discussion.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "What might cause my computer to ____ oddly and even insult me, and how can I fix it?", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You can ____ this book until the end of the school year.", "Opt_1": "retain", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is an obvious ____ to her absences from school: Monday mornings and Friday afternoons!", "Opt_1": "pattern", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is difficult to change an unhealthy eating ____ that has developed from a very early age.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The proposal is unlikely to ____ the tension between them.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "donate", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Here is a good ____ to get paid for conducting undergraduate research at UH through its Summer Research Program.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Both of these programs can be amended as needed to ____ a particular area of vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is not always possible to distinguish a cause of a conflict from a ____ of that conflict.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is ____ the scope of this course.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's not easy to ____ yourself when you're not going out and actually preparing for an opponent.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "interfere", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Each year the school has to ____ many of its textbooks from the USA or England-Germany needs to ____ more qualified computer technicians. It has failed to train enough of its own.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "determine", "Opt_3": "prove", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_3_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "US companies have too often viewed the social sector as a dumping ground for their spare cash, ____ equipment, and tired executives.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The prime minister has said that he has no plan to ____ over the crisis in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There was not a big difference in the negative description of Saddam Hussein ____ the three newspapers, and these descriptions did not occupy much space.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She said sorry to the teacher and ____ avoided a detention.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Excellent writing with just one or two ____ mistakes!", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We should seriously pursue the idea of the internet elections, which are a totally ____ option.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The combination of natural and human systems adds an additional ____ of complexity to the interactions.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Turning in work completed by other students will only ____ you when it comes to the exams.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You must ____ copies of the primary literature that you are citing to your paper, and you should highlight the pertinent sections.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "append", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In closing, I want to assert that I know that our ____ is up to meeting these challenges and I know that the bold and inspiring decisions that will be made.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Repeat this procedure until only a small amount of ____ is released when it is vented.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The police are looking for a woman of ____ height, last seen wearing a red jacket.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a profound ____ on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In order to make student learning ____ to real life experiences, learning environments must be authentic.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The case of Nicaragua demonstrates how the United States failed to ____ on the implementation of democratic procedures.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Only time will settle the ____ about whether the earth really is warming up or not.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The result of such ____ was increased poverty in Russia and lost belief in the fairness of governmental institutions.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The aquarium owner decided sometime in the spring of 1992 to release the animal before any further ____ or an accident with the other dolphins could occur.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is a highly ____ view of the symbolic nature of physical reality.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The last ____ has seen a major transformation of the Indian car industry.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If your ____ is temporary and is impacting only attendance, make sure you follow up with your professors and contact the Dean of Students Office.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Stubbornness is a ____ that is sometimes positive and sometimes negative.", "Opt_1": "trait", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The court decided to ____ the opinion of the mental health specialist.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government's ____ to the demonstrations was to promise a public inquiry into the reasons for going to war.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "response", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the administration failed to ____ its responsibility to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Kaiya reminds him that they have never been ____ before, and it is apparent that Willow is experiencing feelings of guilt.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The university's officials hope that their applications will not drop significantly, though it is too soon to ____ the effect of the hurricane.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "establish", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It started to ____ after much questioning that the reasons for his bad behaviour were problems at home.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "include", "Opt_4": "emerge", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_4_def": "to come out; to become known"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Harvard is probably the most famous education ____ in the USA.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the ____ failed to exert its responsibility to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Teaching is the ____ of the people who work at FIS.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The teachers are not ____ in favour of the school's plan to introduce flexible working times.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first master those principles and then consider the ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "His problems at school started to ____ when he began spending hours on the internet every evening.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "arise", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students must demonstrate evidence of a ____ reading knowledge of a language other than modern English.", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I'm not sure he understands the ____ of the project. He will need to spend at least two hours on it every day for the next 3 weeks.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Please ____ your books and check each other's writing.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The researchers did not ____ people with known chronic disease from their study.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A book published in the regular way must ____ mainly upon its own merits for its success.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The 9-11 Commission failed to ____ or address the multiple war game exercises that were being conducted that day, out of the White House.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "store", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Our experiments with SRM 1010a led us to the conclusion that this was too ____ a method of evaluating results.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "verbal", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Mrs. Cassells did not view us as young children in need of constant guidance, but ____ thought we should have the opportunity to make our own decisions.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Mr. Elliott was at ____ for delegating that function to a person who lacked the experience to perform the job properly.", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "description", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We are not ____ that those who do less well on high-stakes tests in fact do worse in school or on the job.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The study included a ____ of the main concepts of the authors' model on connecting children with nature and community.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "asset", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ problem results from the authors' basic misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company was in a very strong ____ after winning a million dollar contract to build its machines.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Thanks to the accurate description of the witnesses, the police were able to ____ the bank robbers.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The new teacher has been away quite often this year. I speculate that she will not be given a ____ job at the school.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "certain", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "sure", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Please write a ____ summary of the causes of the first world war. Write no more than 300 words.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I prefer to believe that the quality of my thinking has not diminished; I simply have chosen a different ____ to express my ideas.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "format", "Answer": "format", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Why do anthropologists ____ the word 'primitive'?", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The bank did not ____ to make payment but insisted first on the signature of the husband.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Typical conversations ____ a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans accumulate as they grow.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "involve", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "cancel", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to cut or stop from happening"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If a student is not in attendance during the last ____ of a semester, the instructor may report a grade of zero.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "portion", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you ____ from the course by February 12, the course will be deleted from your enrollment record.", "Opt_1": "withdraw", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "After several failed attempts to ____ the dispute by the efforts of the local community, the case was transferred to the City Community Court.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "settle", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will understand the interactions and contributions of the various people and cultures that have lived in or migrated to the ____ that is now Oregon.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She accepted the arduous task of vice president, according to the papers, saying that she could not ____ the will of the people.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is no mechanism in the master plan to ____ whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is ____ the scope of this course.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When two forms of an assessment ____ are equivalent, it should make little difference which one we use.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot ____ its ordinary meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "For the second meeting of the Forum, we have arranged a debate between two legal professionals who must struggle with the death ____ regularly.", "Opt_1": "research", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "penalty", "Opt_1_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When the models incorporate the effects of pollution, they predict that rainfall will ____ even more in the next few decades.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Under these treaties, US warships did not have to ____ the nature of the weapons they carried.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Demonstrators tried to ____ the opening of the new airport runway.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Almost everyone believes that terrorism should be fought, but there is little agreement about the ____ in which it should be done.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "When morality comes up against ____, it is seldom ____ that loses.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "labour", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "work", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Could you please ____ to our Christmas collection for flood victims in Bangladesh?", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government can advise people to save money for old age, but it cannot ____ them to do it.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "achieve", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government needs to overcome its ____ to advising parents how to bring up their children.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "reluctance", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This program will accelerate entry to the ____ and to advanced study of nutrition.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Doctors can give no ____ explanation for the fact that so many people smoke even though they know how dangerous it is.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "rare", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "unusual", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "So far scientists have been unable to ____ in their efforts to find a cure for cancer.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government is going to introduce a law that will ____ smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "release", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to let go or let out"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many students who receive a grade lower than they want, do so because they fail to ____ their texts.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "warn", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government will ____ the situation in Iraq very carefully, but has not yet made any changes in its policy.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government met this morning to ____ how to help people who have been hit by the flood crisis.", "Opt_1": "operation", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you ____ against the school's computer use policy, you will not be permitted to use the computer labs.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I expect each student to put significant ____ into every assignment, providing the foundation for rich and engaging classroom discussions.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This interesting site offers the student of neuroscience access to an ____ amount of information on the discipline.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Recent research shows ____ against African American mothers of any class who don't work.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The demand for oil is likely to increase as people in developing countries such as China and India ____ cars.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "One ____ of the problem that no-one has yet considered is: Who is going to pay?", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was not ____ to use the river as the source for your drinking water before you analyzed it.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "People are more ____ to migrate in times of war or economic poverty.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "My ____ impression is that this plan describes a very ambitious attempt to address an important issue in a scientifically credible manner.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It takes a lot of ____ to cook a meal for 20 guests.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company was in a very strong condition after winning a million dollar ____ to build its machines.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The continued presence of a huge military force in the Gulf ____ provides the necessary element of pressure to ensure implementation of obligations.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In order to self-correct your writing, you need to get an ____ diagnosis of your problems.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is surprising what you can ____ if you make an effort.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Actually if two ____ tones of the same frequency and intensity are produced simultaneously, they will combine.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The value of books would certainly degenerate if they could ____ be produced and reproduced in cyberspace at an extremely minimal cost.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There were complications with the pregnancy, so she had to ____ starting school for a semester.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school offers basketball ____ in the vacation.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is usually easy for teachers to ____ if an ESL student has copied text from a webpage.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "discern", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ to be recognized, to be considered important is not superficial. It is a basic human drive.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We have not yet been able to find out the ____ reason why he attacked the teacher.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Business Index provides a one-stop resource of information on: small business management, foreign ____ opportunities, job hunting strategies.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I do not feel that the possible applications of a line of research should be allowed to dictate the ____ of research in my laboratory.", "Opt_1": "penalty", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "relationship", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I don't believe you made a genuine ____ to improve. Your grades certainly have not got better.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The difference between Japanese and Korean prices gradually decreased until ____ zero where it has remained over the past few years.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government should not ____ its tax policies on what newspaper editors tell it to do.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is a truism that death - not just our own - affects all of us, even if it is a ____ most people do not want to contemplate for long.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "license", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We must be ____ in how we interpret the data. It would be easy to draw false conclusions.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will receive a lengthy, very ____ email, which in short, states that your unsubscribe request did not succeed.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Based on the results, they will have to ____ the tests as often as once every three months or as rarely as once every five years.", "Opt_1": "reward", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "exist", "Answer": "repeat", "Opt_1_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to be alive, to be in the world"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The equator is an ____ line that divides the earth into a northern and southern hemisphere.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government should ____ all its energy to reducing unemployment.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "constitute", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This note describes a scoring ____ for the co-reference task in MUC6.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In the event of an actual ____ a new virtual bulletin board will help the campus take roll.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "disaster", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "a huge problem or failure"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Because of the ____ in the price of oil the company was unable to adhere to its plans to employ new workers.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is not a defect in the notion of economic development as much as it is a problem with the fiscal ____ of Alaska.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly ____ hierarchy of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Being forced to speak before they are ready can ____ some adults' enjoyment and success in learning a language.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "inhibit", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Hopes continue to ____ that a peace treaty can be negotiated.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "reinforce", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school is constructing a new science block ____ the sports field.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ reason for not responding to terrorism was not an external issue, but an internal one: the government failed to fulfill its duties.", "Opt_1": "superior", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "better", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The temperature curve shows that the increase was not ____ with time; a fact which could hardly be expected and is also not observed on other continents.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We need to ____ entry to the cafeteria so that not all students are trying to buy a meal at the same time.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "His research helped establish that ____ DNA sequences may behave differently depending on context and condition.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "characteristic", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "typical"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Army leadership must ____ the importance of reducing energy demand to decrease costs.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Performance in the money markets has been consistent in recent months, but prices are expected to ____ in the near future.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This situation is ____ to improve over the next few years, given the quantity of research now being done on the effectiveness of complementary medicine.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Volleyball players must ____ in order, and every player must do this (i.e. a team may NOT have a designated setter/hitter/etc. who does not ____ out).", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "rotate", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ the idea of having a school uniform. I think it would cause a lot of unnecessary problems.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Unless we ____ the trend, the consequence will be a sustained contraction in the number and quality of staff scientists and research faculty.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will generally include a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a comprehensive final exam.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government had to ____ from its starting position in the face of massive criticism in the newspapers.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There have been ____ attempts to build an intelligent robot, but so far no-one has been successful.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "China also experienced social upheaval, and was unable to ____ foreign domination of its trade.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "terminate", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In order to claim a project, you must ____ a team of 3 to 6 people within a class and get verbal approval from your professor.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Art is every artist's attempt to communicate in a way ____ words what they feel, see, and think about life.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Sediment cores collected from the seafloor off Southern California ____ that plankton populations in the Northeastern Pacific have changed significantly.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "reveal", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to show or uncover"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "To learn a new word, it often helps to make an ____ of it in your mind.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war against Iraq is an appropriate ____ to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You must ____ a bibliography to all reports that are based on information found in books or on the internet.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "append", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not clear to me how you can ____ make cannabis legal and expect the consumption of it to go down.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company made a ____ reduction in its workforce in order to improve its performance in the second part of the financial year.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If men and women do ____ jobs they should earn ____ pay.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "China did not multiply nuclear weapons. Having produced several hundred warheads, China stopped building up its ____ potential.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The writer clearly did not perform the experiment, but gave us what her very great ____ expected would happen.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "form"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When societies ____ into violence the result is all too familiar: the destruction of life and infrastructure, gross abuses of human rights.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "collapse", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ was for travel volume to increase by 1 percent to 2 percent compared to last year.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "forecast", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I was surprised that ____ me there were only about three or four people in favour of the proposal.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "More than 70 percent of the surveyed firms said that the ____ of housing was not a constraint on their ability to expand.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is scheduled to begin at 3:30 p.m. A decision to cancel or ____ the match will be made later in the day, if necessary.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You must write a ____ of 3 pages for your final report.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most employers expect you to ____ a photograph when you apply for a job.", "Opt_1": "recommend", "Opt_2": "speculate", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_2_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You are being quizzed on how well you understand the information in your required readings, so ____ your answers on what is written in the Hunt textbook.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Radio and TV stations often ____ for money from their audience in order to help people suffering from disasters.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "appeal", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's always better to be ____ cautious and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government must not ____ in taking harsh actions against communism and all its supporters.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "For many persons these are not ____ concerns but profound and deep beliefs.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Thorough cleaning must always ____ chemical disinfection of any equipment.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school has a ratio of ____ one teacher for every fifteen students.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We should ____ the error of assuming that we will ever be able to comprehend the causes of his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Harvard is probably the most famous education ____ in the USA.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "statement", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It only drew more ____ to the 13-year-old Robertson panel report and the CIA's role in the investigation of UFOs.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some animals, such as the tortoise or snail, have an external shell ____ than an internal skeleton.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many large companies employ people to analyze a ____ such as the way people spend their money on holiday, etc.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Please remember to ____ any rented vehicle before driving it and note any scratches or other damage to the vehicle on the rental form.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government is heading into difficult ____ with its plans to ban smoking in all public places.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "margin", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The prime minister has decided to ____ the planned visit to Batavia in view of the outbreak of war in the country.", "Opt_1": "inform", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "cancel", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to cut or stop from happening"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Doctors should give uniform advice and ____ to all patients, whether rich or poor.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The only ____ of having computers in the classroom is that they are loud and make the room hot.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "His ____ helped establish that identical DNA sequences may behave differently depending on context and condition.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In some English reported speech sentences you can ____ the word that. For example, He said (that) he was sick.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A great deal of discussion focused on observations which could ____ the mystery by testing the predictions of the various hypotheses.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "appeal", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The study of how computers are similar to human brains is called ____ intelligence or AI.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "artificial", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Art is every artist's attempt to ____ in a way beyond words what they feel, see, and think about life.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government blamed its defeat in the elections on failure to ____ its policies clearly enough.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Since we can't observe it directly, we need to ____ it from the things we can observe.", "Opt_1": "infer", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These ____ and assessment strategies meet the needs of learners who are diverse (e.g., in culture, ethnicity, race, language, special needs).", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In other words, his father did not ____ the level of resources, whether they be human or monetary, necessary for success.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was ____ poorly designed and therefore not worth considering.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A sound card is an essential ____ of a games computer.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Advertising agencies are always looking for ____ ways to sell boring product like washing powder or packet soups.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Doctors ____ make mistakes which can have serious or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some historians still hesitate to ____ the incidents of 1915 as 'genocide ', choosing to use words like 'massacre ' or 'atrocities ' to describe the events instead.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "When does the unborn baby become an ____ separate from its mother?", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Remember that more than one factor may be the cause of a problem and that symptoms may often ____ in their appearance.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "overlap", "Opt_3": "strain", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "overlap", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_3_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Sports events such as the World Cup or the Olympic Games often culminate in an ____ firework display.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "enormous", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The course aims at helping students ____ a working familiarity with the Federal Rules of Evidence.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was agriculture that allowed civilizations to ____ growth.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "raise", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Strauss said his health started to ____ and he was placed on the transplant recipient waiting list.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "decline", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Business Index provides a one-stop ____ of information on: small business management, foreign trade opportunities, job hunting strategies.", "Opt_1": "resource", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many large companies are trying to ____ operations in China. This is the key market of the future.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You may need to ____ to the terms and scope of the permission (i.e., duration, purpose, etc.).", "Opt_1": "distinguish", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "motivate", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government had to ____ that it had not succeeded in its plans to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Board may presume that those actions created a hostile or abusive work ____ which harms the efficiency of the service.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He alleged that the state had adopted the policy of attacking the entire independent media ____ than targeting individual journalists as in the past.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "They all use tools from well outside the natural ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The monks found it difficult to adapt to changes in society and in the economy, and they also found it difficult to adapt to challenges presented by the new learning made available through translations of ____ Greek texts by way of Arabic.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government is thinking of passing a law that will require all house owners to ____ their oil heating system for one that runs on gas.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is a serious ____ of workers in the profession of computer science. The government is hoping to attract qualified workers from overseas to fill the vacancies.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government looks likely to succeed in its ____ to reduce child poverty by the end of the decade.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He did not manage to develop a particularly good ____ in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Can someone please return this science equipment to the ____ cupboard?", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "As each hydrogen only has one electron to share in the formation of chemical bonds, it is impossible to ____ more than two hydrogen atoms to each other.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Whatever I write on the board in class as the next day's assignment will always ____ what is printed in the Class Schedule below.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When a block of wood is gently put into still water, it will descend by the ____ of gravity, until it has displaced a quantity of water, equal to its own.", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is not the only method of teaching we use at the university; ____ we calibrate our teaching techniques to fit our abilities.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Doctors can give no ____ explanation for the fact that so many people smoke even though they know how dangerous it is.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school charges a ____ for outside clubs to use its sports facilities.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A student who fails to cite sources in a deliberate attempt to ____ the source of the work should be considered to be cheating.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There are ____ 100 days until your final examination. It's time you started working.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the administration failed to ____ its responsibility to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "deliver", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school is planning to bring in an ____ tax expert to analyze its finance methods.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Now that you have revised your work, the next ____ of the writing process is to edit it for errors of grammar or spelling.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The police were unable to ____ the demonstrators from the town square.", "Opt_1": "exhaust", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "expel", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to use up", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "One of the most common laments we hear from instructor is that they can't get their students to ____ substantial revisions.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "undertake", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The course introduces students to the structure and function of cities and ways planners ____ urban problems.", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "prove", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It's a total ____ that young girls are being pressured into near-starving themselves into being too thin.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The more alert you are to the key words used and the ____ claims made in ads, the more aware you will become of your own use of words and ideas.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Hopkins argues that the ____ court committed three discrete errors in determining his sentence.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has announced ____ plans to reduce long-term unemployment.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The likely ____ of the accident in the science lab is errors in labelling the chemicals.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "cause", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "the reason why something happens"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There are ____ parts of the planet that have not yet been explored. These are all on the ocean floor.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "discrete", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "separate", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some of the key personal resources that you will draw from ____ your own academic background, teaching style, life experience, and technical experience.", "Opt_1": "include", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "include", "Opt_1_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Because of the shortage of wheat, ____ to persistent wet weather, the price of bread has risen in the last few weeks.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's ____ rigid hierarchy of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "And, further, he didn't appreciate a ____ from one whose own morality has been deficient.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "lecture", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I need to speak to John's parents ____ his constant absence.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Doctors ____ make mistakes which can have serious or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you change your address or place of study, please ____ your log-in details accordingly.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "reform", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After 11 years at the helm of the Scientific Computing Division, Bill Buzbee recently announced his ____ to retire at the end of this year.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Over the course of her journey in the program she has come a great ____ from her primary focus as an agent for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The role of ____ schools in the education of these disturbed children is controversial.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We will also tell you how the ____ to take if you decide to use email as an official means of communication.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ problem results from the authors' basic misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "necessary", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ cause of the accident is that the driver fell asleep, but police are investigating the possibility of a terrorist attack.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Just follow the on-screen instructions as you ____ the discussion forum from within a course.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is often necessary to ____ a mathematical model several times in the course of an urban operations research study.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "revise", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The New Investigator Competition is an award for the best paper by a graduate student, carrying with it a prize valued at ____ \ufffd\ufffd500.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These projects will ____ student learning through the provision of modern technologies.", "Opt_1": "regard", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "enhance", "Opt_1_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many learners of English have problems with the spelling. Furthermore, many Asian students find the articles ____ difficult to use correctly.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The study also ____ that both genders get a similar benefit from the therapy, which reduced mortality risk in women by an estimated 43%.", "Opt_1": "strive", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If we accept your request to ____ the information, we will make reasonable efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the ____ment.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I am ____ that you will do well in the examinations.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some assignments will be graded; others will ____ receive a check-mark.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some people claim that the growth of the internet has been to the ____ of students' ability and willingness to read.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In response to these events, this study was initiated to define and investigate the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first master those principles and then consider the ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We will watch a ____ of films about Ancient Rome. This first one is about Julius Caesar.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The last ____ has seen a major transformation of the Indian car industry.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is a ____ at the school for teachers to share a cake or cookies with their colleagues when it is their birthday.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The first section of this course is concerned with understanding the basic concepts of design: How to ____ and talk about visual material.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "China won't take strong action against Iran's nuclear program because China just made a ____ to buy lots of Iranian oil.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many of the faculty and students we talked with wanted to remain ____ and asked that they not be listed by name in our report.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "anonymous", "Opt_3": "adjacent", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_3_def": "next to", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How to increase employment and reduce crime are the two most serious problems that ____ the new government.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I have a ____ feeling about the forthcoming exams.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "better"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Military historians and other students of international security, ____ got into the habit of meeting together to discuss ideas.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students who take the class are expected to choose a contemporary problem they would like to address and ____ with each other in researching it.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The causes of gun and knife crime ____ young people is an important field of inquiry.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most governments refuse to ____ with kidnappers.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "conduct", "Opt_3": "strain", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_3_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The rising price of oil could result in a ____ economic disaster.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "strict", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Their acquaintance, therefore, it may be presumed, did not ____ till towards the end of this year 1754.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "commence", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I need to speak to John's parents ____ his constant absence.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is my ____ that he copied large parts of your writing from the internet.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You will encounter many difficulties but if you ____ in your efforts, you will succeed.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "arise", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "persist", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Those who had seen the march in Weimar at the 1926 party rally knew that National Socialism's march to ____ could not be halted.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's ____ is, also advises man on woman's potential and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The class learns that Alzheimer's disease is a deterioration of cells within the brain that leads to ____ of memory.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Testing personnel will not confront any tester who is cheating, but will complete the Testing Incident Report and ____ to the supervisor.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "submit", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Teachers can suggest that students get a ____ of 8 hours sleep per night, but they cannot dictate it.", "Opt_1": "plenty", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Every new car that is produced must ____ to standards that minimize pollution.", "Opt_1": "comprise", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Over the same ____ research was unable to measure significant effects on achievement from readily available school characteristics.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "These two-word verbs present one other problem, ____ not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Doctors advise that the better way to get and stay healthy is to eat lots of fruit and vegetables and take ____ exercise.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Under the new programme, employees will continue to ____ the same amount of paid time off as they did in the old programme.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I really need one hundred percent concentration while performing my duties; I cannot be ____ messaging.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Before doing a longer piece of writing it is usually a good idea to make an outline to ____ your main ideas.", "Opt_1": "organize", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "And finally, these estimates depend to some ____ on those proven numbers and, as we've already seen, those numbers are not very reliable.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Over the course of her journey in the program she has come a great ____ from her primary focus as an agent for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "fallacy", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "disaster", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "a huge problem or failure"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "John has many strong opinions. You have to be sure not to let him ____ groupwork in class.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The best way to ensure that your machine has a ____ name is to use your University account name for your computer name.", "Opt_1": "unique", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of young men who walk around with large aggressive dogs is that they are from the working class and are criminals.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Soviet workers have suffered a terrible ____ of a world-historical significance.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The court concluded that the order did not ____ from the essential requirements of law.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}]]